hello mama mushy baby it's pretty marina
Sydney and welcome to love last day
three
[Music]
so in today's vlogmas adventure mama
best we are gonna be doing something
really essential Nanda Baba ha ha -
lucilla ha and as you can see the title
on the best yes we are purchasing life
insurance online isn't it exciting mama
bears na na yan pentagonal Boumediene
and life insurance online just like
sharpie or lazada you can just pop on
your phone and get insured right away
and goo Goo's in your column on how to
purchase your life insurance online then
just keep on watching so recently my my
best FWD life insurance just launched
their new website 3 4 w da chopped up
FWD dot-com that ph and there you go on
a Vespa Kiki Tonya so I know and Yamaha
Pramila Paris 18 today I will be showing
you how I purchased my life insurance
online so without further ado let's get
started using your mobile phone or your
laptop go on your Google Chrome and pie
shop that FWD duck on the pH there guys
mock Akita yo-yo canola can do plans
which includes the unmanned later Kanban
guys you have 100,000 critical illness
coverage which has protection against 42
critical illness no medical tests needed
and six months and need telemedicine
reward so that's really a good deal next
guys is can live can live gives you
200,000 live coverage with essential
funds for your family and one year only
medical consults reward so everything
here guys is really a good deal
next is the can guard Condor gives you
500,000
see them and terrorism coverage which
includes pay out for accidents or terror
attacks worldwide coverage and one-year
global emergency service reward the
insurance has under the can't do plants
is worth one thousand seven hundred
ninety nine per year so that is a very
affordable manga best Halloween
jean-marc subscribe because he would net
flix Gannon but this one guys it gives
you peace of mind who guys wala na
Metallica who my people II don't
everything guys is super solely so here
guys I am going to buy that can live by
nothing new Hanley
I shall leave next up guys is to fill
out all the information including your
name middle name last name sober
nutrients thank you together best your
full name
your informations like birthdays formal
numbers email and then citizenship
it's also very essential to put your
like identification and read all the
declarations properly actually guys I
already read it prior to purchasing it
so and click-click-click Nana clapping
sila after you guys you can do the
payment and then I and you go guys I am
now a FWD life insured there you go guys
na panade know how easy it is to get
your insurance online so before I end
this deal guys I have listed five
benefits of buying your insurance online
so first guy is easy and hassle-free
really easy and hassle-free because you
can buy at the comfort of your home and
office or everywhere regardless of what
clothes you are wearing like a banana
vodka at your comfort zone so very easy
and hassle-free benefit number two guys
no more paperwork and no medical tests
needing so if you're gonna connect
explain you guys because when you buy
talaga life insurance as you have a lot
of papers to do and you have a lot of
meet up with your agent so this one guys
is super benefit number three guys is
you only have few options to get the
best deal keepin your Naaman canina that
I've only got three options the website
numb shop that FWD dot-com so much
mobility Omaha appeal or must
comfortable car
benefit number four guys prop service
yes Papa Panov and it goes right after
you pay you already got your policy and
that is what we always want the Pomona
best booster not a no prop service you
can always manage your insurance on your
government uncle opinion fabulous guys
can you and last but not the least my
best buy your insurance online is really
affordable
is a very good tip doing some online
insurance seeker because you are buying
directly to the company so are you going
on a banana cattle get on video Nagato
para Mac inspire kayo boo be linear in
nagging your mana insurance online I
know guys a lot of us can't afford those
mama Holley insurances by the way guys
WD life insurance corporation is a
licensed by the Insurance Commission of
the Philippines under the new Insurance
Code okay and this is 100% legit so I
hope this you enjoyed watching and if
you do please give this video a big
thumbs up comment any requests down in
the comment section below and please
guys don't forget to subscribe to my
channel : d Capanna hapax absque Ribe
and hit generate on bail notifications
but a not if I fail every time I post a
new video thank you guys so much for
watching and please don't forget the
positive vibes will give you positive
life
maraming salamat merry Christmas
everyone bye
[Music]